v-local.com 2010-04-05

# Privacy

_V-Local.com Privacy Policy_

_Sharing of the Information Gathered on This Site_  
We are the sole owner of the information collected on this site. 

We may disclose your information: 

  * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us. 

  * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our websites' terms and conditions or other agreements or policies. 

  * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, asset sale or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

  * To trusted partners who work on behalf or with V-Local under confidentiality agreements. There companies may use your personal information to help V-Local communicate with you about offers from V-Local and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 

Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies that describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. 

_Information Collected From You By Third Parties_

We may allow third-parties, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements and other materials on our websites, and to deploy technology for our benefit, for example, to load web pages quicker. We and these companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies to collect information about users who view or interact with these advertisements and/or connect to our website. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows us and these companies to deliver and gauge, among other things, the effectiveness of targeted advertisements.

_What Cookies Are and How They Are Used_  
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Our site has programs that use cookies to maintain session information to remember who you are as you go from page to page. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. V-Local may let other companies that advertise on the website set and access their cookies on your computer.

_Changes to this Privacy Policy_  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share personal information that may impact you, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the e-mail address you most recently provided us in your account, profile or registration (unless we do not have such an e-mail address), and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our websites. We recommend that you check our websites from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies. 

_Entire Agreement_. These Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between you and V-Local and governs your use of the V-Local website. 

_Waiver and Severability of Terms_. The failure of V-Local to exercise or enforce any right or provisions of the Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of the Terms of Use is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties’ intentions as reflected in that provision, and other provisions of the Terms of Use shall remain in full force and effect. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with V-Local, please contact us.
